OLAWALE ADEKUNLE

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An insightful Application Development Manager renowned for exceptional leadership and technical prowess, possessing the expertise required to drive teams towards optimal results. Adherence to traditional development lifecycle techniques coexists with the creation of original project-specific protocols, effectively surmounting development output challenges. Demonstrated success in elevating security standards, optimizing planning processes, and proficiently managing systems implementation, including disaster recovery planning and strategy execution.

WORK HISTORY

Application Development Manager, 12/2020 - Current JeanAkins Company, Denver, CO

- Solutions Architect role orchestrating infrastructure to handle client/user traffic while ensuring Data Security.
- DevOps engineer: Managing Front-end and Back-end scripts of business website. Website development and design.
 Troubleshooting and Deployment of application updates
- Application Server, Database, and Systems Administration. Data mining and reporting
- Communicated directly with project stakeholders, providing timely updates on project advancement.
- Identified staff knowledge deficiencies, scheduling educational activities to correct gaps in previous training.
- Maintained 100% scheduled on-time deployment deliverables for application updates

Operations Manager, 02/2022 - 09/2023 Surtek, Inc, Centennial, CO

- Guide analysis of Chemical EOR for project evaluation from initial screening, to fluid study and coreflooding.
- Coordinate weekly project updates with clients that entail technical Interpretation of data results.
- Managed team of 6 lab specialists in fulfillment on different project objectives
- Utilize multivariate analysis in surfactant and polymer considerations for EOR methods in oil and gas fields.
- Verify input data for reservoir simulation on engineering team.
- Core Floods, Rock-Fluid Analysis of Oil & Gas Reservoirs.

- Sugar Land, TX 77498
- (720)-226-2042
- walekunle@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/ooa

SKILLS

- AWS Cloud Practitioner, Solutions Architect and DevOps Engineer
- Database SQL
- Web development and design -HTML, PHP, CSS
- Programming Javascript, Nodejs, Python3
- Multi-Cloud Terraform

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Certified DevOps Engineer Professional DOP-CO2 (Jan 2024)

AWS Certified Solutions Architect Professional SAP-CO2 (Pending)

EDUCATION

Ph.D., Petroleum Engineering, 05/2020 Colorado School of Mines - Golden

Master of Science, Petroleum Engineering, 05/2014 Colorado School of Mines - Golden,

Bachelor of Science, Chemical
Engineering, 11/2008
University of Lagos - Lagos, Nigeria

PUBLICATIONS

Effects of Chemical Osmosis and Swelling on the Elastic Properties of the Pierre Shale and its Implication for Oil *Recovery*, IJRMMS-D-20-00162 (2022). Paper focuses on Low

- Provided technical guidance and training to laboratory staff.
- Managed inventory and supply chain operations to achieve timely and accurate delivery of goods and services
- Supervised operations staff and kept employees compliant with company policies and procedures

Senior Reservoir Engineer, 03/2014 - 01/2020 MTARRI Inc. EORGAS, Golden, CO

- Evaluation of mixed gases containing CO2 and other nonhydrocarbon gases (EORGAS) that provide additional oil recovery at lower pressures in mature fields
- Conduct displacement experiments focused on determining minimum miscibility pressures, solubility of gases in crude oil samples, and oil recovery potential
- Utilize RBA and slim-tube displacement tests to evaluate technical and economic feasibility of EORGAS field application
- Underscore potential savings and applicability of mixed gas technology
- Evaluate potential assets/field targets for EORGAS application; reservoir analysis of existing fields to be used for gas injection pilot tests
- Analyze and report operational cost impacts of displacement experimental data and simulated results to clients
- Recommend injection pressures and volumes on client assets serving as good candidates for EORGAS

Energy Analytics Intern, 06/2018 - 08/2018 S&P Global, Bentek Group, Denver, CO

- Perform quantitative analytics on Oil, Gas, and NGL production from multiple shale gas plays in Appalachian basin
- Enhanced volumetric estimation model accuracy by 90% used in evaluating EUR worldwide
- Utilized queried data from database to monitor seasonality and predict gas production in Appalachian basin
- Optimized decline curve analysis methods for shale gas production data through incorporation of Doung decline method for evaluating shale gas plays in Haynesville, Marcellus, and Utica
- Created weekly reports on pricing, supply, and demand trends for natural gas and NGL (liquids) commodities

Salinity Water Floods as an EOR option in organic-rich shales.

Laboratory study on Property
Alteration from Osmosis Pressure
Distribution in Clay Rich Shales,
URTeC 2019-1088.
Paper highlights how the chemical

Paper highlights how the chemica osmosis process is influenced by changing salinity and effective stress conditions.

Stress-Dependent Permeability and Dynamic Elastic Moduli of Reservoir and Seal Shale, URTeC 2016.
Paper addresses the implications of stress alterations experienced during production and injection in shales.

Experimental and Analytical Methods to Determine MMP for Bakken Formation Crude Oil, JPSE 146 (2016) 170-182.

Paper focuses on viable options for miscible gas injection in the Bakken.